# Michiek van Oosten

### San Francisco



#### **About**

Richard hails from Tulsa. He has earned degrees from the University of Oklahoma and Stanford. (Go Sooners and Cardinals!) Before starting Pied Piper, he worked for Hooli as a part time software developer. While his work focuses on applied information theory, mostly optimizing lossless compression schema of both the length-limited and adaptive variants, his non-work interests range widely, everything from quantum computing to chaos theory. He could tell you about it, but THAT would NOT be a "length-limited" conversation!

Phone: (912) 555-4321
Email: mail@axion5.net
Twitter: @richardhendricks
Github: richardhendricks

# Work Experience Facebook

**Software Engineer** 

2014 - 2012

Give an overview of your responsibilities at the company

Increased profits by 20% from 2011-2012 through viral advertising

#### Education

## University of Oklahoma

#### Information Technology, Bachelor

2011 - 2014

#### Skills

- Web Development
  - o HTML
  - o CSS
  - Javascript
- Compression
  - o Mpeg
  - o MP4
  - o GIF

#### References

It is my pleasure to recommend Richard, his performance working as a consultant for Main St. Company proved that he will be a valuable addition to any company. - **Erlich Bachman**